Long Term Coding Goals
1) https://www.udemy.com/the-complete-web-developer-in-2018/ - Andrei Neagoie
2) https://www.udemy.com/advanced-css-and-sass - Jonas Schmedtmann
3) https://www.udemy.com/understand-javascript - Anthony Alicea
4) https://www.udemy.com/the-complete-junior-to-senior-web-developer-roadmap - Andrei Neagoie
5) https://github.com/getify/You-Dont-Know-JS - Kyle Simpson

Learn to write code by hand on paper and a whiteboard first and then throw it into an IDE for syntax highlighting, this should become second nature to you.
Develop deep knowledge of data structures, their strengths, and weaknesses in comparison to each other. I discovered that implementing data structures and their behaviors from scratch taught me so much more than what I knew from their abstract concepts.
Completely understand Big O notation for both time and space complexities, this will pair perfectly with your algorithm and sorting questions.
Grasp all major sorting algorithms because the difference in time/space complexities have the potential to derail your optimum solution for an algorithm you’re trying to solve.
Resources
Mock Interviews
		interviewing.io (beta), Free
		Pramp, Free
		CareerCup, Paid
Algorithms
		Cracking the Code Interview, Book
		byte by byte, Website and YouTube
		CS50, YouTube
		Interview Cake, Website
		HackerRank, Website
		LeetCode, Website
		
Operating Systems
		Operating System Concepts, Book
Architecture Design
		Intro to Architecture and Systems, YouTube
Behavioural
		Intro to Behavioural Interviews, YouTube
