react

added to a .env file
SKIP_PREFLIGHT_CHECK=true

npm add —only=dev --exact react-scripts@1.0.0
npm upgrade
__________________________________________
React is a variation on the following things:
functions
objects/arrays
classes
callbacks
modules
__________________________________________
render() is the only required method for a React component.
ex:
render() { 
	return ( 
		<div className='ui unstackable items'> Hello, friend! I am a basic React component. </div> 
	); 
	}

There are two ways to declare React components:
(1) As ES6 classes
ex:
class HelloWorld extends React.Component { render() { return(
Hello, world!
) } }

(2) Importing and using the createReactClass() method

Two arguments are often passed to the ReactDOM.render() method.
1) What we’d like to render.
2) Where we’d like it to render.
e.g 
ReactDOM.render([what], [where]);

HTML elements always start with a lowercase letter.
React component names always start with an uppercase letter.

components - a UI component in an app (parent/child components)

props - the way data flows from parent to child in React is through. props are immutable and owned by a component’s parent.

state - owned by the component. when the state or props of a component update, the component will re-render itself. don’t set manually.

JSX attribute values must be delimited by either braces or quotes.

when you define your own custom component methods, you have to manually bind this to the component yourself.

class MyReactComponent extends React.Component { constructor(props) { 
super(props);   // always call this first 

// custom method bindings here 
this.someFunction = this.someFunction.bind(this); 
	}
}

again, when defining custom methods on React component classes, you must perform the binding pattern inside constructor() so that this references your component. by calling super(props), we’re invoking that constructor() function first.

it’s a good practice to always call super() first whenever you declare a constructor() for your component.
_________________________________________________

When adding state to a component, the first thing we do is define what the initial state should look like.


1. Break the app into components 2. Build a static version of the app 3. Determine what should be stateful 4. Determine in which component each piece of state should live
5. Hard-code initial states 6. Add inverse data flow
7. Add server communication

Classes when you need state, Functions when you don’t need state.
__________________________________________________
a controlled component is only showing what is in state….
__________________________________________________
Make as few copies as possible…
Transformation done with function below…
__________________________________________________
Call this.setState in componentDidMount() {
}
__________________________________________________
render() {
	if (this.state.order.length ===0) {
		return (
__________________________________________________
Mounting - these methods are called when an instance of a component 
is being created and inserted into the DOM:
1) constructor()
2) componentWillMount()
3) render()
4) componentDidMount()
Updating - an update can be caused by changes to props or state. These
methods are called when a component is being re-rendered.
1) componentWillReceiveProps()
2) shouldComponentUpdate()
3) componentWillUpdate()
4) render()
5) componentDidUpdate()
Unmounting- this method is called when a component is being removed from the DOM:
1) componentDidUnmount()

